if you are marketing coaching training
mentoring online what is the best
landing page structure that's actually
going to get you sales for those of you
haven't met yet my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and I have been helping mentors
coaches and Trainers for the last 21
years scale their businesses to tens of
millions of dollar I've personally built
multiple coaching businesses over $10
million a year in profit and I help
people who are just getting started put
together the puzzle pieces that actually
get results for them if you want to get
clients you got to grow your email list
it's one of the number one things that
you have to do and to be able to do that
the right way you got to have a landing
page that gets people to sign up to your
email list so there's a structure that I
love to teach people to use for this
that works the best here's the thing is
that you need to be able to get very
very specific about the outcome that you
can deliver about who it's for and then
communicate that in a way that very
quickly within 5 to 10 seconds helps
people make a decision of if they should
trust you or not the truth is this is
that people's judgments are Split Second
when somebody lands on your landing page
this is generally the process of how
they're going to end up finding you
they're going to find you either on
social media they're going to find you
maybe on a podcast they might find you
on YouTube maybe they'll find you on
Google something like that right some
place on the internet that're that
they're going to find you and they're
looking looking for a solution okay so
anytime somebody is going to find you
they're seeking a solution unless you
are a famous celebrity that has millions
and millions of followers already I can
tell you this I've actually worked with
a number of them that do and I've helped
them scale their businesses even those
people who have millions of followers
people are looking for a solution when
they find them and nothing else okay and
so what you want to do is you want to
send these people all these people right
here to
a landing
page and that landing page gives them
very quickly the kind of information
that they need to make the right
decision every landing page always has
at the top of it
a headline now I've worked with some of
the top marketers in the world and I've
seen people make the biggest mistakes on
the planet and I can tell you what the
biggest mistake is is talking way too
much about what you do for people what
you sell what you coach on and that's
one of the biggest problems if you're a
great coach or Mentor you've studied a
lot of stuff and you've applied yourself
to become a master at a certain topic
and you're proud of that and you want
people to know what you can help them
with the problem is is
this there's a thousand other people
that also help people with those same
things and so the only thing that sets
you apart is being able to grab people
emotionally and get them to make a
decision on this one thing can you help
me better than anybody else solve my
immediate problem quickly and that's
what people are looking for so your
headline is always going to be based on
the outcome that's going to be delivered
as well as mentioning who it's for I'm
going to give you an example of this on
a couple of landing pages that we've
created here I got two offers recently
that we that we put up they generated
tens of thousands of dollars in our
businesses and this right here is one
where I talk about who it's for at the
top there's a headline the ultimate cure
for Burnout and overwhelmed for coaches
who want to make real revenue and
profits in their business without
selling their soul start bringing in
truly consistent six figure clients on
autopilot working 10 to 15 hours a week
and right here we have this where I'm
talking about creating and launching a
community offer here's another one right
here that we went and put together this
was for a health offer and this one did
extremely
well marketed through social media and
Facebook ads turn back the clock and
take charge of your body instead of it
being in control of you even if you
failed every other approach now you'll
notice the difference between these two
this one over here has a whoops that was
another landing page right there that I
was also looking at from another another
coach that's out there another great
landing page structure very similar but
right
here you'll see we have a header right
here that has
a um a photo of me right there it has
the title of the event this was a live
event on Wednesday that we were hosting
right here this is a video that talks
about what this is and then we have
another headline below it Fitness
hormones wellness and more are you tired
of fighting your body and being
exhausted all the time okay next after
that the structure that we have is and
this is the part that people get wrong
below that they end up
putting a section that should be a story
that draws people in this is called the
story section of the landing
page the story section talks about the
experience it talks about what the
outcome is going to be it emotionally
grabs people it has an image that draws
people into the story if we scroll down
on this page right here we have this
section the story section right here
what is going to be delivered is not
necessarily what's what's talked about
but how they're going to experience it
and it talks about the the the struggles
and the frustrations people have come
out of from this
okay it has a photograph of somebody
right here who is an image of who the
offer is for so no matter what landing
page you're creating this structure
works as far as this goes okay now you
could do a short form landing page you
could do a long form landing page for
events I like to do a bit of a of a
hybrid approach couple of paragraphs
right here we have another headline down
here in the middle that kind of breaks
it up and that's another thing we like
like to do I like to add in another
headline about halfway down right there
breaks it up a little
bit a section about who I am on this
page what's going to be
delivered and then we go into if we have
any bonuses
testimonies and the call to action at
the bottom there okay same over here we
have more on what's going to be
delivered a bold promise you can Thrive
you can succeed you can turn your whole
life around you can experience Health
like this your best Life Starts
Now what they're going to get out of it
this is a whole section that contains
what is going to be included any bonuses
and then it says sold out now but there
was links to purchase on there right
there so the structure of this always
follows this three-step formula you have
a story section right here this is what
most people miss when they're creating
their landing pages is they end up
skipping that story
section completely skip it because all
they care about is telling people what
they're going to deliver you want the
what section to come after you
emotionally draw people in with the
headline and then the
story of what they're going to
experience and the story is something
like this it it shows
empathy it invites them into a
conversation it invites them into an
experience have you ever never wondered
how to experience the best health of
your life maybe you've tried everything
before and it's not worked we're telling
their story back to them are you a coach
who's tried to build a business but
you've struggled and you put in hours
and hours and hours and can't seem to
make the kind of money that you want to
make this is a story that your prospect
and what you're doing is you're speaking
directly to who the prospect is what
they're struggling with and what the
outcome is that they're looking for okay
so when we create a landing page with
these two features right here you're
winning the problem that I see that most
people do is they are leading with what
they deliver what's taught in it when it
is how it's being delivered how many
modules are in it I get it you care
about that they care about it only after
they buy into it emotionally so people
make decisions based on emotion and
logic together but the emotion and
feeling part of it comes first
I mean a lot of great coaches out there
and they don't get this right because
they think that what they are delivering
is what matters the
most it's about connecting with people
emotionally and drawing them into
something that's going to persuade them
that it's worth their time to work with
with you okay so then from here at the
bottom we have a call to action and this
is where people sign up with their name
and email address and they put in their
name and email address and so this
structure for a landing page this is the
structure that is going to work for you
in your funnels whether you're
delivering an ebook whether you're
delivering a free course whether you're
delivering a master class of some kind
whether you're you're hosting a live
event or a challenge this structure
allows you to create a vision in
people's minds as to what they are going
to experience and so when they see it
when they visit it when they land on it
they start to feel what it's going to be
like on the other side of purchasing
from you okay now what we like to do to
be able to create a lot of this copy
right here is I use a series of prompts
in chat GPT we have a chat GPT document
over my website that I've actually put
together it's free right here um
download these chat GPT prompts you can
go grab that over at my website right
here and it's a Google doc that you can
grab and there's a series of incredible
promps for creating sales letters that
you can use it helps you come up with
the pain points helps you come up with
the Epiphany Bridge all of that and so
listen if you are a coach Mentor trainer
somebody who is trying to get more
clients you have to learn how to
communicate in a way create a landing
page that actually gets people to buy
into the thing that you're trying to
express to them now what's the best way
to build build a landing page like this
there's a lot of great landing page
builders that are out there personally
one of my favorites is actually using
Squarespace and the reason why I love
Squarespace is it's all drag and drop if
you go over to squarespace.com you can
play around with their Landing Page
Builder and and you can check this out
for free doesn't cost you anything to be
able to do this which is really really
cool I was just playing around with this
yesterday uh building out a a site right
here here um for
a for an offer that we were creating for
a for a training course that I was
putting together and I'm just going to
show you what one one of these Pages
looks like
okay we can have a Graphic at the top
you could use canva to create a graphic
right there you have a headline we can
create some stock images with AI I like
to use meta to create stock images right
here you can go in under under imagine
you can and you can type in you know uh
a woman
experiencing painfree birth with her
husband um happy with baby after
birth me
see baby
after okay and and listen some of these
prompts that they don't it doesn't
necessarily want to create because it's
like oh I can't generate that okay
that's fine fine but what if it's like
what if it's like
this there we
go okay and so you can use AI to
generate this as far as Graphics go
images this is great right here you
could literally use this if like that's
a course that you're something like that
so it generates great like stock images
that you could use that look really good
as well chat GPT is another great
resource that can do this for you so
using AI to be able to put together a
lot of different features of your
landing pages of your sales copy of the
images that you're using is a great way
to tell the story it's a great way to
connect with people effectively and it's
a great way
to engage emotionally with people the
right way okay and so when you're doing
this you can use a builder like
Squarespace to be able to put something
like this together and here's what I
love about Squarespace let's just check
this out watch we can edit this page
right here and I can literally just drag
these images around the page I can
resize them I can see what it looks like
on desktop and mobile right here here's
some sales copy right here that we
wrote we have this uh right here we add
in uh maybe an appointment scheduling or
a subscribe form all of that's built
right into Squarespace and you can
easily put this together using a
Squarespace account it cost you less
than I think like 30 bucks to be able to
create a Squarespace account to put
something like this
together and it's worth it to invest in
your business it's worth it to invest
into tools like that to start to build
things that are effective for you in
your business you know one of the
biggest things that I noticed that a lot
of people do is they don't take action
and they don't do anything in their
business and they're constantly tossing
around all these ideas they're watching
YouTube videos they're not getting the
kind of help they need in their business
and that's exactly what I love to work
with people on in my accelerator program
has help them break past those
limitations that are holding them back
where they're struggling to even take
action where they might have an idea of
how they want to help people but they're
not able to reach people and so listen
I'd love to encourage you to just go
check that out over at my website uh
Jeremiah Kowski doccom you can go find
my client growth accelerator right here
get on the waiting list for it I'd love
to work with you in there to help you
build your coaching business to start to
make the kind of money that you want to
make if you're not growing an email list
and then you're not consistently selling
to people how do you expect to be able
to make the kind of money that you want
to make and so what we have to do is we
have to learn how to figure out who do
we want to work with how do we promote
our offer to the right people at the
right time and communicate in a way that
draws them into the conversation with us
so that then we can present and make a
presentation to sell to people if you're
a coach or Mentor the only way that
you're going to be able to make the kind
of money that you want to make is by
learning effective messaging and
persuasion and so after somebody signs
up with your landing page
offer whatever they're signing up for
you need to use that to then persuade
them to become a client of yours after
the fact okay and so what that means is
whether it be an ebook you need to have
a call to action for something whether
it be booking a call with you or a live
event that you have or a link to a a
trial some kind of incentivized low
commitment way of working with you
further after that initial offer that
they make it's really romantic to
imagine that people are going to come
back to your website and find you and
want to become a client of yours but the
truth is that's really not how it works
out and so we have to be intentional to
get people to sign up on our email lists
and then once they're there we're
intentional to make sure we're sending
them emails we're leading them to the
different offers that we have and we're
following up with people so that they
actually step
into wanting to work with us becoming a
client of ours and getting deeper into
our ecosystem you know just having a
great coaching program isn't enough just
having a landing page isn't enough but
you got to learn how to communicate well
with people to be able to do this you
got to learn how to communicate through
video content to be able to do this and
and I'll tell you this that video
content especially if you start creating
content like this on YouTube is a great
way to practice your chops to get more
um confidence in your ability to
communicate with people to reach people
and to let them know what you have to
offer you probably have something
amazing and incredible to offer people
but who's going to know about it if they
don't know that you have something to
offer well they're going to go find me
on my website that's not really how it
works so you got to be intentional to
actually tell people about what you have
to offer that's why what we do is we
create a landing page a lead magnet
something that gets people on our email
list that's related to what their
desires are what do they want what are
they dealing with what problem can you
lead them to a solution with and so when
you can take a group of people that are
out there and you're able to lead them
to a solution that you have to offer
based on something that they very
specifically are dealing with that you
can help them through now you're able to
build trust with them and send them
another offer another glass another
engagement with you
something else that they're going to
want to go to the next level with you on
okay so like what that means is like
let's say somebody signs up for a free
ebook and now you you have a webinar or
you have a training or something like
that you're going to want to then follow
up with people and send that to them
after the fact send them after the fact
the offer that you have that's going to
take them from point A to point B to
point C okay so it's about being
intentional that you go and find those
people that are looking for what you
have to offer they exist out there
whether it be through social media
whether it be they're on different
platforms it's your job to funnel them
down into your email list to get them
into your ecosystem so then you can sell
to them so then you can connect with
them if you're not doing this they're
not going to become clients of yours
okay and so that's exactly the process
that I teach people to do and this is
one of those pieces is putting together
a landing page that actually gets people
to sign up to your email list as far as
that goes okay I meet so many people
they over complicate the the process of
creating their landing page I meet
people that they take years to even do
this right here why because they feel
like they're not ready yet they feel
like they're
not good enough to put something out
there can I tell you
this waiting until you feel ready yet is
not going to make you more ready you
know I me I meet people all the time
they have incredible training and
coaching and offers that they can put
out there and they're waiting until they
feel ready enough to put themselves out
there and the thing that I notice is
that the the best thing that they could
possibly do is just to take action stop
waiting until they feel ready stop
waiting until it's like the perfect
scenario and just start connecting with
people the only way that you're going to
get clients in your coaching business is
by connecting with people by learning
how to communicate in a way
that brings connection that keeps people
hooked and engaged with you they want to
listen to you they want to follow what
you're talking about you become a leader
to people that they can look up
to and then you're able to lead them to
the thing the outcome the solution that
you offer you know many times we just
expect people to just find us and become
clients of ours and that doesn't
actually happen that way we got to be
intentional to go out there to find
those people people and then we end up
attracting them by how we present
ourselves as far as that goes has
nothing to do with how you dress has
nothing to do with how you look at all
when I talk about present yourself it
has everything to do with the words you
say and how you communicate the words
that you use to communicate your value
to people and so by using AI we can help
brainstorm and come up with some of
those ideas for what those words are and
then put them onto landing pages that
can help us connect with our Target
client and so listen if you are a coach
Mentor trainer and you're somebody
that's looking to dial in your messaging
and get more clients and sell more I
want to work with you in my accelerator
program to bring those pieces together
to put those puzzle pieces together so
that you can start to find the clients
that you're looking for
okay you don't have to struggle you
don't have to wonder is this going to
work if you apply a proven system that's
worked like with thousands of people
that I've worked worked with over the
years that's worked with clients that we
have right now in my program that have
generated tens of thousands of dollars
and even millions of dollars in their
business like Judy she made over
$37,000 working with me applying this
training in her s in her business or
like Dr shandu Who made $112,000 his
first time out as far as that
goes you know I meet so many great
coaches and mentors that are out there
and they they're not putting themselves
out there
they they they're not reaching clients
maybe they have a few one-on-one clients
that they've gotten over the years but
they're burnt out they're stressed out
and so it's time to shift that and move
into what I call the group coaching
riches model where you start to get
people into your business in a group
coaching program you get them to join
you in a
group and this helps save you time this
helps save you effort it helps save you
energy
trying to convince people that they
should become clients yours trying to
convince them of what you need to do
oneon-one because you get to build a
community and an audience of people that
are engaged with you they want what you
have to deliver and they they get to
work with you together in a way that
optimizes your time in the best way if
you are a mentor or a coach you got to
learn how to optimize your time so that
you're not working for dollars for hours
trading the hours that you have every
single day for money but rather you're
able to connect with people in a group
and make recurring Revenue off of that
group that's paying you by being a part
of a group Community as far as that goes
okay and so that's why we want to build
a landing page that attracts those
people to us we want to create offers
that draw people in to what we have to
do and then we want to present to that
group of people to sell them the thing
that we want you don't need to do all of
this crazy hours and hours and hours
with the stuff it's actually very very
simple if you just can create one offer
one landing page communicate simply with
people and then learn how to sell to
them with confidence learn how to learn
how to get them to buy into the thing
that you are
delivering there's way too many great
coaches out there that are just they're
struggling way too hard they're working
way too hard and they're not making the
kind of money they want to make and I
don't want that to be you and I want you
to start to make the kind of money that
I know is possible for you like it has
been for my clients and like you can
accomplish in your own business when you
start to communicate in a way that's
powerful when you start to show up
online in a way that's GNA get people to
want to listen to you that's going to
get people to want to engage with you
that's going to get
people leaning forward because they
actually care about what you're talking
about and then taking
action when you send them an offer when
you invite them into your program
because that's what I experience in my
business and that's what you're going to
experience as well if you start to apply
a process like this so listen love to
work with you in my accelerator program
love to get you those kind of results
listen subscribe to this channel we keep
we roll out videos every every single
week multiple times a week you can go
check out all the different videos that
we have on this channel different topics
on on what to put together in your
business when you learn to communicate
in a way through the internet through a
landing page that actually brings people
into your ecosystem gets them to say yes
to you instead of just maybe you can
have a sustainable successful business I
know that you can and I'd love to help
you get there all right we'll talk soon
have a good one